# Chaitanya S

## UI/UX designer Full-stack designer

chaitanyauxdesigner@gmail.com

My Portfolio link

+91 7569496182 | 9542909009

#### Skills

Ux research, UI design, Create personas, Information architecture, competitive analysis, high fidelity wire-frames, prototypes, HTML 5, Css3, SASS, Bootstrap, Responsive Web design.

#### **Awards**

Received Insta Award at Infosys

#### Certifications

Full-stack design certification SAP Fiori 3 design system

## Hobbies

Pinting

Drawing

Planting

Science Experiments

#### Tools

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe illustrator

Adobe sketchbook

Procreate

AutoCADD

Appzillon3.10

Miro

"I love to work in a progressive environment where I can utilize my knowledge and experience to learn new skills and also get involved in being a part of a winning team. I am a cognitive designer with about 2+ years of experience in user experience design, 1+ in story board Artist and 1+ in Auto CADD designing industrial experience."

## **Work Experience**

## Wongdoody + Infosys

Mar2021 - till date

Associate-experience Designer

I Delighted to worked with Fortune 500MNC, where I had chance to explored designing across a variety of domains. Meanwhile, continuously skill up through the in-house training's and initiatives.

below are the few projects which i have worked in Wongdoody journey

#### Online Banking application

Working with a team of developers and designers as Full-stack designer/ UX unicorn to create online banking responsive design application where my role is to collaborate with designers to create high fidelity designs and achieve the same in development.

#### • Banking platform Design Syatem

Worked in Digital Banking Processing Platforms for Retail and Corporate Banking by Independent Research Firm where the responsibility is to develop what we designed.

#### Government TAX Agency

worked as a UX researcher to enhance user experience for a native mobile application where the final outcome was 50% faster completion of form-filling task and 60% screen reduction with all functionalities compared to existing screens and also we achieved zero deficiency delivery and received Insta Award for best rating from client.

#### DA portal

lead 2+ designers to Designed and presented native flows for a Employee well being share-point intranet portal.

#### • Agriculture domain

Worked as a visual designer for design System in global agriculture white label company

## Inucom Pvt LTD

Sep2020 - Feb2021

### Story board Artist & SME

worked as a freelancer Story board artist to create story boards for visual impact of the story line, which help 3D Artists to create 3D, 2D videos making along with it I worked as SME for Electrical concepts.

## M.Govind & sons

Aprl2013 - Sep2014

## Design Engineer

Responsibility to create Auto CAD Design layouts, plans, design samples for automatic bailing cotton press machines and hydraulic machines. A key achievement was pointed out design failure of tilting cotton press design and I had provided the design solution to overcome the existing failure.

## **Education Qualifications**

BFA, Applied Arts in JNAFA University, Hyderabad (70%).

Intermediate, M.P.C in G.C.SS.Jr college, Guntur (85%).

2016-2020

2008-2012

**BTech**, EEE in Narasaraopet institute of technology, Guntur (75%).

2006-2008

S.S.C in G.C.SS. High School, Guntur (88.2%).

2005-2006